[
  {
    "question": "You are designing an ecommerce web application that will scale to hundreds of thousands of concurrent users. Which database technology is best suited to hold the session state in this example?",
    "options": [
      "Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS)",
      "Amazon DynamoDB",
      "Amazon Redshift",
      "Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3)"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "You need to find an item in an Amazon DynamoDB table using an attribute other than the item's primary key. Which of the following operations should you use?",
    "options": [
      "PutItem",
      "Scan",
      "Query",
      "GetItem"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "In Amazon DynamoDB, what does the query operation enable you to do?",
    "options": [
      "Query a table using the partition key and an optional sort key filter",
      "Query any secondary indexes that exist for a table",
      "Efficiently retrieve items from a table or secondary index",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which AWS Cloud service is best suited for analyzing your data by using standard structured query language (SQL) and your existing business intelligence (BI) tools?",
    "options": [
      "Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS)",
      "Amazon Simple Storage Service Glacier",
      "Amazon DynamoDB",
      "Amazon Redshift"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "In Amazon DynamoDB, an attribute is",
    "options": [
      "a fundamental data element",
      "a collection of items",
      "a collection of attributes"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "If you are developing an application that requires a database with extremely fast performance, fast scalability, and flexibility in the database schema, which service should you consider?",
    "options": [
      "Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS)",
      "Amazon ElastiCache",
      "Amazon DynamoDB",
      "Amazon Redshift"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following use cases is appropriate for using Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS)?",
    "options": [
      "Massive read/write rates",
      "Simple GET or PUT requests",
      "Complex transactions",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "A company has an application, which consists of a .NET layer that connects to a MySQL database. They want to move this application on to AWS and use AWS features such as high availability and automated backups. Which of the following would be an ideal database for this use case?",
    "options": [
      "Amazon Redshift",
      "Amazon DynamoDB",
      "Amazon RDS",
      "Amazon Aurora"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Amazon RDS automatically patches the database software and backs up your database, storing the backups for a user-defined retention period and enabling point-in-time recovery.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What should you consider when choosing a database type?",
    "options": [
      "Data size",
      "Data access period",
      "Query frequency",
      "Highly available",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following Database Services is a NoSQL Database",
    "options": [
      "Amazon Aurora",
      "Amazon RDS",
      "Amazon DynamoDB",
      "Amazon Redshift"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which relational database is a proprietary technology from AWS and is cloud-optimized?",
    "options": [
      "DynamoDB",
      "Oracle",
      "Athena",
      "Aurora"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "You would like to set up a NoSQL database that can scale with no downtime and can handle millions of requests per second. Which AWS database is best suited for this work?",
    "options": [
      "DynamoDB",
      "RDS",
      "Redshift",
      "Athena"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "RDS is a Serverless database",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "NoSQL Databases have flexible schemas for building modern applications",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  }
]